Guide to the Western Filmscript Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Western Filmscripts Acquired Before July 1996, 1918-1989
  - Overland Mail, December 18, 1941 - January 21, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 257a)
    Director: Ford Beebe John Rawlins
    Producer: Henry MacRae
    Actors: Lon Chaney, Jr. Helen Parrish Don Terry
    Notes: Serial. Folder A: Chapters 1-7.
  - Overland Mail, December 18, 1941 - January 21, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 257b)
    Notes: Serial. Folder B: Chapters 8-15.
  - The Overland Telegraph, February 4, 1929 (Box 36, Folder 258)
    Screenplay: [George C. Hull]
    Director: [John Waters]
    Actors: [Tim McCoy Dorothy Janis Frank Rice]
  - Overland Trails, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 259)
    Screenplay: Jess Bowers (Adele Buffington)
    Director: [Lambert Hillyer]
    Producer: [Barney Sarecky]
    Actors: [Johnny Mack Brown Raymond Hatton Virginia Belmont]
    Production company: Great Western Productions
    Setting: "Gold Flats" mining town
    Notes: "script of Mr. Burrows"
  - The Ox-Bow Incident, November 17, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 260)
    Story: Walter van Tilburg Clark
    Director: William A. Wellman
    Producer: Lamar Trotti
    Actors: Henry Fonda Dana Andrews Mary Beth Hughes
    Type: Continuity and dialogue from the screen
  - The Pagan, August 7, 1928 (Box 36, Folder 261)
    Story: John Russell
    Screenplay: Frances Marron
    Notes: second part in synopsis from
  - Paint Your Wagon, April 24, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 262)
    Screenplay: [Alan Jay Lerner]
    Director: [Joshua Logan]
    Producer: [Alan Jay Lerner]
    Actors: Lee Marvin Clint Eastwood [Jean Seberg]
    Setting: Gold rush
    Notes: Musical. Marked "Jerry Barlow/1365 Magnolia/Apt. 27/Redding 96601."
  - Pale Rider, 1985 release (Box 37, Folder 263)
    Screenplay: Michael Butler Dennis Shryack
    Producer: [Clint Eastwood]
    Actors: [Clint Eastwood Michael Moriarty Carrie Snodgress]
    Setting: Carbon Canyon
    Notes: Two copies.
  - The Parson of Panamint, [1941 release] (Box 37, Folder 264)
    Story: Peter B. Kyne
    Screenplay: Harold Shumate [Adrian Scott]
    Director: [William McGann]
    Actors: [Charles Ruggles Ellen Drew Philip Terry]
  - Pecos River, February 9, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 265)
    Screenplay: Barry Shipman
    Director: Fred F. Sears
    Actors: Charles Starrett Smiley Burnette Jack (Jock) Mahoney
    Notes: The Durango Kid series. "Charles Starrett" written on cover. Working title: Whiphand
  - Perils of the Royal Mounted, [1942] (Box 37, Folder 266)
    Screenplay: Basil Dickey Scott Littleton Louis Heifetz [Jesse Duffy]
    Director: [James Horne]
    Producer: [Larry Darmour]
    Actors: [Robert Stevens Nell O'Day Herbert Rawlinson]
    Production company: [Columbia Pictures]
    Setting: Canada
    Notes: Serial - 15 episodes, separately paginated
  - The Persuader (Subtitle: Trouble in the Territory), 1957 release (Box 38, Folder 267)
    Screenplay: Curtis Kenyon Dick Ross
    Director: [Dick Ross]
    Actors: [James Craig Kristine Miller William Talman]
    Production company: World Wide Pictures
    Type: Final revised
  - Phantom Cowboy, February 5, 1941 (Box 38, Folder 268)
    Screenplay: [Doris Schroeder]
    Actors: [Don Barry Virginia Carroll Milburn Stone]
    Setting: Raynor County
  - Pistole, revised July 18, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 269)
    Story: William P. Bagwell
    Screenplay: Bernard B. Bossick
    Director: Bernard B. Bossick
    Producer: William P. Bagwell
    Actors: Barry Finchman Barbara Benson Gus Peters
    Production company: Bagwell Films
    Notes: Newspaper trade clipping taped to first page. Actor names written in next to cast list
  - The Plainsman, September 3, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 270)
    Producer: Richard E. Lyons [Jack Leewood]
    Actors: [Don Murray Guy Stockwell Abby Dalton]
    Production company: Universal TV
    Setting: Fort Harper
    Type: Second revision
  - Pony Soldier, February 26, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 271)
    Story: Garnett Weston
    Screenplay: John D. Higgins
    Director: [Joseph M. Newman]
    Producer: [Samuel M. Engel]
    Actors: [Tyrone Power Cameron Mitchell Thomas Gomez]
    Setting: 1876, Canada
  - Posse, August 6, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 272)
    Story: [Christopher Knopf]
    Screenplay: William Roberts [Christopher Knopf]
    Director: Kirk Douglas
    Producer: Kirk Douglas
    Actors: Kirk Douglas Bruce Dern Bo Hopkins
    Production company: Bryna Company
    Setting: Tesota, 1892
  - Powder River, April 11, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 273)
    Story: [Sam Hellman]
    Screenplay: [Geoffrey Homes]
    Director: [Louis King]
    Producer: [Andre Hakim]
    Actors: [Rory Calhoun Corinne Calvet Cameron Mitchell]
    Setting: Arizona, 1877
  - Powder River, August 15, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 274)
    Screenplay: Richard Wormser
  - The Proud Ones, December 5, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 275)
    Story: [Verne Athanas]
    Screenplay: Joseph Petracca [Edward North]
    Director: [Robert D. Webb]
    Producer: [Robert L. Jacks]
    Actors: [Robert Ryan Virginia Mayo Jeffrey Hunter]
    Setting: Kansas
  - Quick Triggers, May 17, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 276)
    Screenplay: Patricia Harper
  - Raiders of San Joaquin, June 4, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 277)
    Story: Patricia Harper
    Screenplay: Elmer Clifton Morgan B. Cox
    Actors: [John Mack Brown Tex Ritter Fuzzy Knight]
    Setting: California, 1892
  - Raiders of San Joaquin, March 14, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 278)
    Story: [Patricia Harper]
    Screenplay: Oliver Drake [Elmer Clifton] [Morgan B. Cox]
    Actors: Fuzzy Knight Johnny Mack Brown Tex Ritter
    Type: Notes on synopsis
  - Raiders of San Joaquin, [1942] (Box 39, Folder 279)
    Screenplay: Elmer Clifton Oliver Drake [Morgan B. Cox]
    Actors: [Johnny Mack Brown Fuzzy Knight Tex Ritter]
  - Raiders of San Joaquin, June 25, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 280)
    Actors: Johnny Mack Brown Fuzzy Knight Tex Ritter
    Notes: Based on story outline.
  - Rainbow Valley, [1935 release] (Box 39, Folder 281)
    Screenplay: Lindsley Parsons
    Director: Robert N. Bradley
    Producer: Paul Malvern
    Actors: John Wayne Lucile Browne George Hayes
    Production company: [Lone Star]
    Setting: Early twentieth century
    Notes: "Bell Hyer" scribbled on front. With revisions.
  - Rancho Grande, December 5, 1939 - January 29, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 282)
    Screenplay: Betty Burbridge Connie Lee [Bradford Ropes] [Peter Milne]
    Producer: William Berke (assoc)
    Actors: Gene Autry Smiley Burnette June Storey
    Type: Treatment and shooting script
    Notes: three distinct sections bound together.
  - Range War, July 15, 1949 (Box 39, Folder 283)
    Setting: Wyoming, turn of the century
  - Rawhide, December 16, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 284)
    Actors: [Tyrone Power Susan Hayward Hugh Marlowe]
    Setting: Rawhide
    Notes: 'Darryl Zanuck' copy with signature. With correspondence.
  - Rawhide, January 6, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 285)
  - Redwood Valley, April 12, 1954 (Box 40, Folder 286)
  - Renegades of the Rio Grande, July 25, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 287)
    Director: Howard Bretherton
    Actors: Rod Cameron Fuzzy Knight Jennifer Holt
  - Renegades of the Rio Grande, July 28, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 288)
    Notes: "Willis Cook" on front cover.
  - Reprisal, February 29, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 289)
    Story: [Arthur Gordon]
    Screenplay: Raphael Hayes [David P. Harmon David Dortort]
    Producer: [Lewis J. Rachmil]
    Actors: [Guy Madison Felicia Farr Kathryn Grant]
  - The Return of a Man Called Horse, [1976 release] (Box 40, Folder 290)
    Director: [Irving Kerschner]
    Actors: [Richard Harris Ana DeSade Gale Sondergaard]
    Production company: Sandy Howard Productions
    Setting: Mandan country, 1830
  - The Return of the Cisco Kid, February 6, 1939 (Box 41, Folder 291)
    Screenplay: [Milton Sperling]
    Director: Herbert I. Leeds
    Producer: [Kenneth MacGowan]
    Actors: [Warner Baxter Lynn Bari Cesar Romero]
    Type: Shooting final
    Notes: wardrobe plot sheets attached, with detailed handwritten costume details.
  - Rhythm on the Range, March 24, 1936 (Box 41, Folder 292)
    Story: [Mervin Houser]
    Screenplay: [Walter DeLeon Frances Martin John Moffitt] [Sidney Salkow]
    Director: [Norman Taurog]
    Actors: Bing Crosby Frances Farmer Martha Raye
  - "Riddle" Gawne, 1918 (Box 41, Folder 293)
    Screenplay: Charles Alden Seltzer
    Producer: Thomas H. Ince
    Actors: William S. Hart Katharine McDonald Lon Chaney
    Production company: Aircraft Pictures
    Notes: script printed on half sheets in packets by reel
  - Ride a Crooked Trail, August 12, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 294)
    Story: [Borden Chase]
    Screenplay: Borden Chase [George Bruce]
    Director: [Jesse Hibbe]
    Producer: [Howard Pine]
    Actors: [Audie Murphy Gia Scala Walter Matthau]
    Setting: Little Rock
    Notes: "Audie Murphy" written on cover. Working titles: Ride a Crooked Mile, Middle of the Street.
  - Ride, Tenderfoot, Ride, June 19, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 295)
    Screenplay: Winston Miller
    Producer: William Burke (assoc)
  - Riders of Ghost City (Box 41, Folder 296)
    Screenplay: Luci Ward Morgan B. Cox Ray Taylor
    Notes: serial - 13 episodes
  - Riders of the Dawn, 1945 release (Box 42, Folder 297)
    Story: Bert Horswell
    Screenplay: Louise Rousseau
    Director: Oliver Drake
    Producer: Charles J. Bigelow
    Actors: Jimmy Wakely Lee "Lasses" White Phyllis Adair
    Production company: Monogram
  - Riders of the Purple Sage, July 10, 1931 (Box 42, Folder 298)
    Screenplay: John F. Goodrich Philip Klein Barry Connors
    Director: Hamilton MacFadden
    Producer: Edmund Grainger (assoc)
    Actors: [George O'Brien Marguerite Churchill Noah Beery]
  - Riders of the Rockies, [1937 release] (Box 42, Folder 299)
    Story: [Lindsley Parsons]
    Screenplay: [Robert Emmett]
    Director: [R. N. Bradbury]
    Producer: [Edward Finney]
    Actors: [Tex Ritter Louise Stanley Charles King]
    Production company: [Grand National]
    Distributor: [Grand National]
  - Rio Conchos, January 22, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 300)
    Story: [Clair Huffaker]
    Screenplay: Joseph Landon [Clair Huffaker]
    Director: [Gordon Douglas]
    Producer: [David Weisbart]
    Actors: [Richard Boone Stuart Whitman Tony Franciosa]
    Setting: Texas/Mexico, 1867
    Notes: Revisions from April 1964. Working title: Guns of Rio Conchos
  - The Road to Many a Wonder (Box 42, Folder 301)
    Story: David Wagoner
    Screenplay: Frank Perry
    Production company: F. B. Productions
    Setting: Nebraska Territory, 1859
  - The Romance of Cow Hollow, February 13, 1919 (Box 42, Folder 302)
    Story: Charles Kenyon
    Screenplay: Charles Kenyon
  - Rooster Cogburn, July 22, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 303)
    Story: Charles Portis
    Screenplay: Martin Julien (Martha Hyer)
    Director: [Stuart Miller]
    Producer: [Hal B. Wallis]
    Actors: [John Wayne Katharine Hepburn Anthony Zerbe]
    Setting: Western District of Arkansas
    Notes: Clean script.
  - Rose Marie, May 27, 1953 (Box 42, Folder 304)
    Story: [Oscar Hammerstein II Otto A. Harbach]
    Screenplay: Ronald Miller George Froeschel Dorothy Kingsley
    Director: Mervyn LeRoy
    Producer: [Mervyn LeRoy]
    Actors: [Ann Blyth Howard Keel Fernando Lamas]
  - Rough Ridin' Justice, February 23, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 305)
    Producer: Jack Fier
    Actors: Charles Starrett Jack Ingram Jimmy Wakely
    Setting: Salt Springs, 1890s
    Notes: Shooting schedule included. Complete version of "Darling Clementine". "Starrett" and "Derwin Abrahams" on cover. Working title: Cattle Call.
  - Round-up Time in Texas, 1936 (Box 43, Folder 306)
    Actors: Gene Autry Smiley Burnette [Maxine Doyle]
    Setting: Texas, twentieth century
    Notes: Singing cowboy picture.
  - Rovin' Tumbleweeds, December 21, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 307)
    Screenplay: Betty Burbridge Dorrell McGowan Stuart McGowan
    Actors: Gene Autry Smiley Burnette Mary Carlisle
    Notes: Date handwritten on first page. Carbon copy. Working title: Washington Cowboy
  - San Antonio, August 26, 1944 (Box 43, Folder 308)
    Screenplay: Alan LeMay W.R. Burnett
    Director: [David Butler]
    Producer: [Robert Buckner]
    Actors: [Errol Flynn Alexis Smith Florence Bates]
    Setting: San Antonio, Texas
  - The Savage, May 19, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 309)
    Screenplay: Sydney Boehm
    Producer: Mel Epstein
    Actors: Charlton Heston Susan Morrow Joan Taylor
    Notes: Changes enclosed. "Troy Sanders" on front cover. Working title: Warbonnet
  - The Scalphunters, May 14, 1962 [1968 release] (Box 43, Folder 310)
    Story: [William Norton]
    Screenplay: William Norton Alex Nicol
    Director: Sydney Pollack
    Producer: [Jules Levy Arthur Gardner Arnold Laven]
    Actors: [Burt Lancaster Shelley Winters Telly Savalas]
    Notes: handwritten notes enclosed
  - Scandalous John, August 26, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 311)
    Story: Richard Gardner
    Screenplay: Bill Walsh Don DaGradi
    Director: [Robert Butler]
    Producer: [Bill Walsh]
    Actors: [Brian Keith Alfonso Arau Michele Carey]
    Production company: Walt Disney Productions
    Distributor: [Buena Vista]
    Notes: on cover "William O'Connell; Role - clerk in men's store"
  - The Scarlet Horseman, 1946 release (Box 43, Folder 312)
    Screenplay: Joseph O'Donnell Patricia Harper Tom Gibson
    Director: Ray Taylor Lewis D. Collins
    Producer: Morgan Cox
    Actors: Paul Guilfoyle Peter Cookson Virginia Christine
    Type: Master copy
    Notes: Serial - 11 parts, separately paginated. Working title: The Scarlet Horseman Rides Again. Handwritten notes: "This copy contains corrections that are in no others." Chapter 1: "This is the only chapter of the serial that is ready for breakdown. All others must undergo First Revision--and then my budget revision."
  - Second Time Around, April 11, 1961 (Box 44, Folder 313)
    Story: Richard Emery Roberts
    Screenplay: Clair Huffaker Sally Benson Oscar Saul [Cecil Dan Hansen]
    Director: [Vincent Sherman]
    Producer: [Jack Cunningham]
    Actors: Debbie Reynolds Steve Forrest Andy Griffith
    Setting: Arizona, 1911
    Notes: Movie review included. Working title: Star in the West
  - Seminole Uprising, June 25, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 314)
    Story: [Curt Brandon]
    Screenplay: Robert E. Kent
    Director: [Earl Bellamy]
    Producer: [Sam Katzman]
    Actors: [George Montgomery Karin Booth William Fawcett]
    Production company: Clover Productions
    Notes: With revisions. Working title: Bugle's Wake.
  - Seven Angry Men, August 20, 1954 (Box 44, Folder 315)
    Director: [Charles Marquis Warren]
    Producer: Vincent M. Fennelly
    Actors: [Raymond Massey Debra Paget Jeffrey Hunter]
    Notes: Working title: John Brown's Raiders.
  - Sheriff of Las Vegas, July 7, 1944 (Box 44, Folder 316)
    Screenplay: Norman S. Hall
    Producer: Stephen Auer (assoc)
    Actors: Bobby Blake John Hamilton Jay Kirby
    Setting: Las Vegas, 1895
    Notes: Red Ryder series. Actors written in on cast list
  - Short Grass, [1950 release] (Box 44, Folder 317)
    Screenplay: Tom Blackburn
    Producer: [Scott Dunlap]
    Actors: [Rod Cameron Cathy Downs Johnny Mack Brown]
    Production company: Filmcraft Trading Corporation
  - Sierra Stranger, [1957 release] (Box 44, Folder 318)
    Screenplay: Richard Dorso
    Director: [Lee Sholem]
    Actors: [Howard Duff Gloria McGhee Dick Foran]
    Setting: Northern California, 1849
    Notes: Working title: The Stubborn Man.
  - The Silver Bullet, March 5, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 319)
    Story: [Oliver Drake]
    Screenplay: [Elizabeth Beecher]
    Director: [Joseph H. Lewis]
    Producer: [Will Cowan (assoc)]
    Actors: Johnny Mack Brown [Fuzzy Knight Jennifer Holt]
    Setting: 1890's
    Notes: Marked "Oliver Drake, Rush, Filmed" on cover. Revisions included.
  - The Silver Bullet, May 21, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 320)
    Notes: Includes official synopsis.
  - Silver City Bonanza, October 17, 1950 (Box 44, Folder 321)
    Director: George Blair
    Producer: Melville Tucker (assoc)
    Actors: [Rex Allen Buddy Ebsen Mary Ellen Kay]
    Setting: mining country, 1900
  - Silver Dollar, July 22, 1932 (Box 44, Folder 322)
    Story: David Krasner
    Screenplay: Harvey Thew Carl Erickson
    Director: [Alfred E. Green]
    Actors: [Edward G. Robinson Bebe Daniels Aline MacMahon]
    Distributor: First National Distribution
    Setting: St. Charles
  - Silver Valley (Box 45, Folder 323)
    Screenplay: Harold B. Lipsitz
    Actors: Tom Mix [Dorothy Dwan Philo McCullough]
    Production company: William Fox Company
  - The Singing Cowboy, [1936 release] (Box 45, Folder 324)
    Story: [Tom Gibson]
    Screenplay: [Dorrell McGowan Stuart McGowan]
    Director: [Mack V. Wright]
    Producer: [Nat Levine]
    Actors: Gene Autry [Smiley Burnette Lois Wilde]
    Notes: Musical.
  - Singing Hills, March 3, 1941 (Box 45, Folder 325)
    Screenplay: Olive Cooper
    Director: Lew Landers
    Actors: Gene Autry Smiley Burnette Virginia Dale
    Production company: Republic Studios
    Distributor: Republic Studios
  - Singing on the Trail, April 23, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 326)
    Screenplay: J. Benton Cheney
    Director: [Ray Nazarro]
    Producer: [Colbert Clark]
    Actors: [Ken Curtis Jeff Donnell Guy Kibbee]
    Notes: on cover "Prop Shop - Mel Wolf"
  - The Singing Sheriff, March 31, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 327)
    Screenplay: Eugene Conrad Henry Blankfort
    Director: Leslie Goodwins
    Producer: Bernard Burton (assoc)
    Actors: Bob Crosby Fay McKenzie Edward Norris
    Setting: small Western town; Alabama
    Notes: enclosed "At-A-Glance."
  - Sioux Blood (Box 45, Folder 328)
    Screenplay: Houston Branch George C. Hull
    Director: John Waters
    Actors: Tim McCoy Robert Frazer Marian Douglas
  - Six Gun Gospel, [1943 release] (Box 45, Folder 329)
    Story: Ed Earl Repp
    Screenplay: Jess Bowers (Adele Buffington) Ed Earl Repp
    Actors: [Johnny Mack Brown Raymond Hatton Inna Gest]
    Setting: Goldville
  - Six-Gun Justice, May 15, 1946 (Box 45, Folder 330)
    Story: Sherman Lowe
  - Skin Game, January 13, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 331)
    Story: [Richard Alan Simmons]
    Screenplay: Peter Stone David Giler [Pierre Marton]
    Director: [Paul Bogart]
    Producer: Harry Keller
    Actors: [James Garner Lou Gossett Susan Clark]
    Production company: Cherokee Productions
    Setting: Missouri, 1857
  - Slade, June, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 332)
    Screenplay: Warren Douglas
    Director: Harold Schuster
    Producer: Lindsley Parsons
    Actors: [Mark Stevens Dorothy Malone Barton MacLane]
    Production company: Lindsley Parsons Productions, Inc.
    Notes: Working title: Jack Slade
  - Smoky Canyon, April 4, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 333)
    Notes: "Durango Kid" series
  - Soldier Blue, October 10, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 334)
    Story: [Theodore V. Olsen]
    Director: [Ralph Nelson]
    Actors: [Candice Bergen Peter Strauss Donald Pleasence]
    Production company: Katzka-Loeb Productions
    Distributor: Avco Embassy
    Setting: Snake Flats
  - Son of the Morning Star, March 12, 1990 (Box 141)
    Story: Evan S. Connell
    Screenplay: Melissa Mathison
    Production company: Republic Pictures Corporation
  - Sons of the Gun (Box 46, Folder 335)
    Story: Mickey Rooney
    Screenplay: Michael Kraike Mickey Rooney
  - South of the Border, September 27, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 336)
    Screenplay: Betty Burbridge Gerald Geraghty [Dorrell McGowan Stuart McGowan]
    Type: Synopsis - outline
    Notes: "Betty Burbridge" written on cover. Copy of theme song enclosed.
  - The Spoilers, April 2, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 337)
    Story: Rex Beach
    Screenplay: Lawrence Hazard Tom Reed
    Director: Ray Enright
    Actors: Marlene Dietrich Randolph Scott John Wayne
    Production company: Frank Lloyd Productions
    Setting: Nome, 1900s
    Type: Dialogue
  - Springfield Rifle, April 17, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 338)
    Story: [Sloan Nibley]
    Screenplay: Charles Marquis Warren Frank Davis
    Director: Andre de Toth
    Producer: [Louis F. Edelman]
    Actors: Gary Cooper [Phyllis Thaxter David Brian]
    Setting: 1864
    Notes: includes shooting schedule, detailed cast list
  - Stagecoach, November 14, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 339)
    Screenplay: [Dudley Nichols]
    Producer: [Walter Wanger]
    Actors: [Claire Trevor John Wayne Thomas Mitchell]
    Setting: On stagecoach going West
    Notes: Belonged to Kay Frankel, New York City
  - Stagecoach, April 9, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 340)
    Story: [Ernest Haycox Dudley Nichols]
    Screenplay: Joseph Landon
    Producer: Martin Rackin
    Actors: [Ann-Margret Red Buttons Michael Connors]
    Production company: Martin Rackin Productions
    Notes: Remake of 1939 version.
  - Stagecoach, June 15, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 341)
    Producer: [Martin Rackin]
    Actors: [Alex Cord Ann-Margret Red Buttons]
    Setting: On stagecoach going West.
    Notes: Remake of 1939 version
  - The Stalking Moon, December 15, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 342)
    Screenplay: Alvin Sargent [Wendell Mayes]
    Director: Robert Mulligan
    Producer: [Alan J. Pakula]
    Actors: [Gregory Peck Eva Marie Saint Robert Forster]
    Production company: National-General
    Distributor: National-General
    Type: Unrevised
  - The Stalking Moon, January 30, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 343)
    Director: [Robert Mulligan]
    Notes: "Gregory Peck" written on cover. Revisions dated 1/30/68.
  - Stars Fall on Arizona (Subtitle: Shooting Star) (Box 47, Folder 344)
    Type: Roughly typed synopsis
  - Sundown on the Range (Box 47, Folder 345)
    Screenplay: Jack Natteford
  - Sunset in El Dorado, April 19, 1945 (Box 47, Folder 346)
    Story: [Leon Abrams]
    Screenplay: John K. Butler
    Actors: Roy Rogers [Dale Evans George Hayes]
    Notes: "Roy Rogers" written on cover.
  - Sunset Trail, May 19, 1938 (Box 47, Folder 347)
    Setting: Santos, Arizona, 1881
    Notes: Hopalong Cassidy series. Working title: Silver Trail Patrol.
  - Support Your Local Sheriff!, November 29, 1968 (Box 47, Folder 348)
    Producer: William Finnegan William Bowers
    Actors: James Garner Joan Hackett Walter Brennan
    Setting: Colorado, mining country
  - Tall Man Riding, June 10, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 349)
    Screenplay: Joseph Hoffamn
    Actors: Randolph Scott Dorothy Malone Peggie Castle
    Notes: Many handwritten annotations, including schedule on inside front cover, actors names on cast list, etc.
  - The Tall Men, March 7, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 350)
    Story: [Clay Fisher]
    Screenplay: [Sidney Boehm Frank S. Nugent]
    Producer: [William A. Bacher William B. Hawks]
    Actors: [Clark Gable Jane Russell Robert Ryan]
    Setting: Montana, 1967
    Notes: Contains revisions from April 1955.
  - Tell Them Willie Boy is Here, January 2, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 351)
    Story: [Harry Lawton]
    Screenplay: Abraham Lincoln Polonsky
    Director: [Abraham Lincoln Polonsky]
    Producer: Philip A. Waxman
    Actors: [Robert Redford Katharine Ross Robert Blake]
    Setting: California, 1909
    Notes: Working title: Willie Boy.
  - Ten Wanted Men, April 8, 1954 (Box 48, Folder 352)
    Story: [Irving Ravetch Harriet Frank Jr]
    Screenplay: [Kenneth Gamet]
    Director: [Bruce Humberstone]
    Actors: [Randolph Scott Jocelyn Brando Richard Boone]
    Production company: Scott-Brown Productions
    Setting: Silver City
    Notes: With shooting schedule.
  - Tender Mercies, [1982 release] (Box 48, Folder 353)
    Screenplay: Horton Foote
    Director: [Bruce Beresford]
    Producer: [Philip S. Hobel Mary-Ann Hobel Horton Foote Robert Duvall]
    Actors: [Robert Duvall Tess Harper Betty Buckley]
    Production company: [EMI Productions]
    Setting: Contemporary Texas
    Notes: In library binding, withdrawn from Emerson College
  - Tequila Sunrise, January 14, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 354)
    Director: [Robert Towne]
    Producer: [Thom Mount]